Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
The hero's name was Lumiere Silver Million Clover.
He was later hailed as the first Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Outro Music
風が背中を張って シスクは糸を伝って Get's up
目を覚ましてよ Get down もう間もなく
Outro Music
We can kiss the game
lists of the love we can kiss the game
Don't haveMerغus ni connotation
You're ready
We can kiss the gale
Let's finish up in the dark
Let's keep the wait
If you kiss the game
Back to the capital.
Yes, I realize she's just returned, but I do have an official order.
Well, it appears to be legitimate.
There's no need to worry, ma'am. We'll take every precaution to get her there safely.
As soon as Marie comes home from battle, they summon her to the capital again.
I can't imagine what the magic parliament could possibly want with a child her age.
Sister Teresa!
Is something wrong, Rebecca?
There's trouble. Look at this. It's today's paper.
Is this true? It can't be! No! Why?
Look what they said about Asta!
Ah! Oh!
Wait a minute!
Turning against the kingdom. Serving a devil?
Lies! Not one bit of it is true!
Looks like that snuck-nosed commoner showed his true colors.
He's such a loser!
Does that mean Asta will have to come and work here too?
This is so exciting, I can't wait to dissect him!
He promised me I could!
Who cares?
Geez, why are you so angry?
I'm not angry!
Whoa, your blood is boiling!
I know! Maybe I should drain a few pints of it!
That'll fix you!
Hell no!
Wait a sec!
Why do I have to put up with all this nonsense anyway?
Hey, Valtos! What am I doing in this garbage heap?
Who knows? It's not my fault you decided to follow me.
I came here so I could atone for my sins.
You're so damn useless!
I'll cut you villains limb from limb if you don't get to work now!
We can't work if you keep on attacking!
You'll kill us!
Crazy cleave!
What do you think I care?
If I had my way, you'd been carved up like dinner hams as soon as I laid eyes on you!
Go on! Run away!
Give me an excuse to use my blades!
You call us villains?
You're the most violent one here!
When you die, I'll make your corpse into a puppet!
I'll bind you with my chains!
Shut up!
Asta!
They're mad!
Asta didn't do anything wrong!
They can't make him take the blame for our crimes!
But they can, Klaus!
I mean, we're talking about Donatio here!
He's ruthless!
They say he's even judged his own father!
He gives cruel punishments, and he never shows mercy!
No matter what!
They'll punish him and anyone attached to him!
This doesn't look good!
Let's hope they don't find Asta guilty!
He looks hideous!
Just like the legends!
He's a devil!
You've finally shown us your true self, you monster!
I can change into my dark form quicker now!
After that last fight, I'm learning how to make it my own!
I'm so scared!
You'll be fine, Marie.
Promise.
I'm not gonna let them hurt you.
Okay.
Now everybody, listen up!
Don't panic!
I can control my power, so there's no need to be afraid!
I'm not dangerous!
Why should we believe what you say?
You're possessed!
I can't bear to look at him!
He's disgusting!
You're just a street urchin who made a deal with a devil!
Put him to death!
I knew the boy was trash all along!
Devil?
Oh dear!
A treasonous commoner like him deserves nothing less than the death penalty!
Harsh!
Please just listen for a sec!
Kill him before he wreaks even more havoc on our kingdom!
What more evidence do you need?
Give up, boy.
Even if you managed to defeat me and escape this trial, you would only become a fugitive.
There's nowhere for you to run.
And if you do flee, I'm afraid I can't assure the safety of the people in the church who raised you.
So the best option is for you to be convicted here and now.
You are a dangerous entity that needs to disappear.
And once you do, that little girl and the magic knights will be spared.
No one in this room nor in this whole kingdom can save you.
And none of them has any desire to.
You bring despair and calamity to everything you touch.
Which means you are evil.
What's happening?
What?
Who's there?
I was told the trial would be held two days from now.
I should have known you clowns were going to try to play by your own rules.
Anyway, I came here to say I don't give a rat's ass if a kid's evil or not.
He might be younger than me, but I've decided that Asta's a real man's man, not to mention a total badass.
And he's a really good friend of mine.
So there's no way I'm going to stand here and let you convict him.
If you lay one finger on my best pal, you'll be cursed for all of eternity.
And I've transformed into Asta before!
I know how brave he is and I want to be like that someday!
Asta's a super good boy!
He's nice!
Marie would be sad if you died, so I guess I don't mind saving you along with her.
But you better take your hands off her!
He may be a boy, but in my eyes he's a courageous young man who can make even the cruelest fates bounce right off him.
I couldn't ask for a better partner. In fact, he makes me look good just being his superior.
So many snacks he hasn't tried! It would be a crime if he died now!
He's a stupid little shrimp.
But I'm willing to admit, he's pretty close to what a magic knight is supposed to be.
I mean, kind of.
He's a loud, reckless, obnoxious idiot.
But as royalty, I have to admit he's a person the kingdom can't do without.
But it's not that I would really care one way or the other.
We're not leaving here without him.
Give Asta back!
Ah yes, the Black Bulls.
What's that strange vehicle of theirs?
They have no right to be here!
How dare you disturb these honorable proceedings!
Yamisuki Hiro.
Am I to understand that you and your companions are defending the criminal who started this great war?
I trust you know what will happen to the Black Bulls as a result of your foolishness.
Obviously, you haven't heard of us.
We're basically the worst Magic Knight squad that ever existed.
And both of those brats with the horns are members.
Oh, me too?
You messed with our squad mates.
So call us Riff Raff, Rebels, whatever.
We're here to take back what's ours!
You guys came.
You may be innocent, but you're still going to be punished for touching Marie.
What now, brother?
Let him be!
I can't believe you were gullible enough to walk into a trap I warned you about!
What, are you too stupid to keep yourself alive for five minutes?
Obviously, he is.
This is a great time for a duel!
The day you die is the day I die!
Put Marie down right now or I'll give you the death penalty myself!
I thought you guys were here to save me!
Stop it, big brother!
That's an odd way of thanking someone for protecting your sister.
Thanks for locking up my squad members, you royal jackass.
Real nice justice you got there.
Please don't worry about me, sir!
Take Asta and get out of here!
I'm not from this era.
And because of the forbidden magic, I'm not even a human anymore.
Besides, I basically used you to complete my mission.
You've got some nerve saying all that stuff after I let you crash at our hideout for so long.
You've been watching us forever, and somehow you still don't get it.
Oh yeah, I heard all about you.
So you were kicking ass as a little bird for 500 years?
How awesome is that?
And all by yourself.
You must have been so lonely, poor thing.
I definitely know what that feels like.
We can always use another beautiful young lady on the team.
You worked hard in the shadows.
So we'd probably get along really well.
I would ask if you and I could be friends.
Except, we've been best friends since the moment I was born.
Um, yes, please join us!
You've seen all the fun we have together.
Now you can be a part of it too.
Just promise me you'll share your snacks!
Wow, it's a good thing I didn't need her back when she was a bird.
Tell me I didn't hear that.
Look, the Black Bulls are a wacky group of misfits.
So if you're worried about being too different for us, you must not have been paying attention.
Besides, I'm already familiar with your key.
Trust me, one more weirdo isn't gonna hurt anything.
Are you sure?
Sealing magic.
Eternal prison.
In that case, I'll join you.
Sounds good.
Our squad's rep is as pitch black as it gets anyway.
That's us!
Like us or not, we are the Black Bulls!
It seems I haven't made myself clear.
Even if you protect that devil's cohorts, it won't change the outcome at all.
Causing a fuss here won't clear the criminal's name.
In fact, the charges against him for conspiring with a devil will become more severe.
Your impassioned pleas for your friend will do nothing to help the kingdom.
These nobles will never change their minds.
They're swayed by bewilderment and suspicion.
And even if they did revolt...
Scale magic.
Scale regulating.
Whoa! My poor sheep!
He's drinking!
My scale measures spells.
It judges your magic, balances it, and creates order.
No matter how powerful you are, you can't win.
But Rouge hasn't disappeared.
Which means he won't be able to do anything to us.
And we have someone on our side who can make the impossible possible.
Demon destroyer sword!
Fate release!
Did he just erase the effects of my magic?
Your move, Justice Boy.
Justice Boy.
If it isn't the foreigner, you're as reckless as always, I see.
What exactly were you planning to do next?
Uh, I usually make things up as I go along.
It almost looked like you were trying to miss.
You brute.
But even if you did this to rescue your squad members, you still couldn't have made a worse impression.
Though it did by some time.
What is with the big lizard?
Wow, you really came back with a bang, didn't you, tough guy?
Now it's you guys?
So how many people are gonna bust in here?
In light of recent events, we can't afford to lose any strong magic knights.
Regardless of our difference in status, we still acknowledge you and your squad mates as valuable allies.
Now Zell is here, and Vrygoleon too.
Those magic knights are both royals.
Why are they here?
Is there something I can do for you?
We've been given a message from the Wizard King.
It's for the Black Bulls.
A special mission.
You are to locate and investigate these devils.
You will prove your innocence with your own hands.
Oh, I get it.
Royals have the authority here.
That's why he sent Nozel and Vrygoleon.
Who better than them to make these snobs listen?
Sometimes I think that geriatric kid really can see the future.
That Julius?
Why must he reappear just in time to step on my toes again?
I guess this means Asta won't be put to death, at least for now.
While Asta is occupied with this assignment,
the Wizard King and the rest of the magic knights will be taking full responsibility for him.
So they're creating leeway for the scoundrel to prove his innocence,
while also giving the impression that he's being dealt with by Julius and the magic knights.
Wait, what does that mean though?
I'm confused.
We're gonna go investigate those devils,
to prove you're not evil and save your ass.
And we'll break the curse of the forbidden magic, too.
Investigate the devils!
What? That doesn't solve anything.
It's an order from the Wizard King.
There must be a reason.
Plus two royal captains are vouching for him.
And the Wizard King said he would take responsibility.
Apparently this audience isn't as cynical toward you as I predicted they'd be.
But know this.
If you prove to be of no use to the kingdom, you will be executed.
Your fate continues to hang in the balance.
Come.
Right.
Marie.
I'm glad you're safe.
Save it!
I told you not to attack Asta and you still didn't listen!
What? Marie!
Hey, I just want to say, thanks for your help.
If you want to thank someone, then you should thank the Wizard King instead.
I will.
Asta, here.
Huh?
What was that thing? A trick?
It's a device that can track your location.
This way, we know you won't be able to flee or hide.
Do you really think I would run away?
We know you won't.
But, there are times when one has to put up a front.
You see?
Sir.
You got off easy this time.
Eh, buddy?
You really had us worried there.
Oh, you must be up-hurried.
Bet you could use a drink.
I'm right second, too!
I'll feed you myself if you like, friend.
I missed you!
Lucky little moron.
I also can't breathe me!
I'll be so near!
Come in?
Pardon me.
Ah, Damnatio!
So, despite your current state, you're trying to take care of everything again.
The Magic Knights and that Devil-Possessed Boy.
That was a clever move, wasn't it?
Now no one has to get punished.
Well, I think that's how it should be, since Asta never did anything wrong.
I'm fairly confident that the Black Bulls will learn something useful about the Devils.
That should make up for them barging into the trial uninvited.
Forgiving them means taking responsibility.
The Kingdom can't bear a burden that great.
And neither can you, for that matter.
But I didn't forgive them.
I trusted them.
Those things don't always go hand in hand.
You know, I think eventually, your scales will tip in Asta's favor.
I'm relieved your personality didn't change with your face.
This land is in danger.
The crisis we're facing is not a small one.
If the Kingdom starts to fall, I must pass judgment.
Upon that boy, and even upon you.
Farewell.
Your Majesty!
Marks!
It's good to see you.
Seems you're feeling better already.
You're alive, but you're younger.
How can you be so young and alive?
I'm fine, thank you.
I'm more concerned about you, sir.
You're...
Where do I even start?
You were always a bit like a child.
And now you really are a child.
Well, it's like this.
No, you don't need to explain.
You can just show me your memories later.
The Kingdom is facing peril.
And with you stuck in that form...
Honestly...
You act so damn ridiculous.
But...
I'm really happy.
That you're still alive.
Thank you, Marks.
I'm sorry for making you worry all the time.
No.
You're not forgiven.
Huh?
First, you have lots of work to do.
Wait!
There are plenty of problems that need your attention, sir.
Right now?
あー...
You're not forgiven.
But when people hear me...
I'm not...
I'm so sorry.
Who's going on to take it off?
I go.
一人 過
散躍
퍼 小さ fortun?
甘え る記憶が
影を広げた
まだ止まない雨
居場所を示す足跡はやがて消えてしまうから
新しいページを今開こう
恐れずに先頭で旗を振ったを
向かいが強いほど高くまで飛べるから
Just take my hand 今日を生きる君に
明日が待っている
ベタバル
There's Trouble
Sister Theresa
Is something wrong, Rebecca?
There's Trouble
Look at this
It's today's paper
What? This is...
What this is?
Would someone please finish the sentence?
I agree. Come on, this is what?
A masterpiece!
Five hundred years ago, a terrible tragedy created a grudge between humans and elves.
And it was all caused by a devil.
Black Clover, page 123.
Narrow Reminisces, part one.
About two mysteries, you learned how to die.
You're not stayed late, but...
To be continued...
Once you came to discover, what might it lastivesse you againет?
I won't wait for you guys, but you don't want to see me up here.
It does seem like that.
Once we are done, we put you lots and whickets on our recommended list,
then, too, totally special.
Go to God3.